Action
Начинаем
Move
Вперёд
Ordered to investigate stolen supplies
По приказу провожу обыск
Those who resist
Кто окажет сопротивление
Will be executed on the spot
будет казнён на месте
Search
Обыскать
A mob
Просто толпа сброда
Didn't expect it to be so easy
Не ожидал что так легко взяли
Don't you think
Тебе не кажется
Things went too smoothly?
что всё идёт слишком гладко
Here
Я
Report
Докладываю
No grain found in the warehouse
В складе нет провианта
Only weapons and armor
одно оружие и доспехи
What?
Что
Report
Докладываю
A unit of elite troops
Отряд элитных войск
Is approaching us
движется к нам
Elite troops
Элитные войска
Now besides the city defense troops
Кроме городской стражи
Where else are there troops?
откуда здесь войска
I see on the banner
Я видел на знамени
The character "Zu"
иероглиф Цзу
It's the border army
Пограничные войска
Oh no
Плохо
We've been tricked
Это ловушка
Go
Отступаем
Rebellious son
Предатель
This rebellious son
Проклятый мятежник
So impatient?
Не мог дождаться
Your Majesty
Ваше Величество
The capital is now in constant danger
Сейчас столица в опасности
Your subject requests
Прошу
To immediately deploy border troops to suppress the rebels
немедленно призвать пограничные войска для подавления мятежа
Yes
Да
Yes, yes, yes
Да да да
Zu Kun returned to the capital to report
Цзу Кунь вернулся с докладом
My border army is nearby
Мои пограничные войска как раз поблизости
Who's leading them again?
Как его зовут того командира
General Fenwei
Генерал Фэнвэй
Zu Yue
Цзу Юэ
Retreat
Отступаем
Retreat, retreat
Отступаем Быстрее
Prince of Jin has rebelled
Принц Цзинь поднял мятеж
I am ordered to capture him
По императорскому приказу арестовать
Surrender
Сдавайтесь без сопротивления
And your lives will be spared
и сохраните жизнь
I give you three breaths
Даю вам три счёта
Drop your weapons
бросайте оружие
Three
Три
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
Inside are only armor and weapons
Внутри полно доспехов и оружия
Let's fight our way out
Прорвёмся
Two
Два